<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Fashion industry is among the leading corporations that gain international recognition. Over the past decade, the industry has attained impeccable recognition both locally and international. Despite the recognition, what many people do not understand is that it takes strategy and planning in order to gain such popularity. Fashion industries are not only limited to clothes and shoes but may also include other brands such as designer perfumes, hand bags among others. According to the research conducted by the Apparel market group, fashion industry is rated as among the top companies with the biggest turnover in turns of returns. Additionally, the industry is also among the top with the highest market appeal.
In order to survive the market and competition, the corporations need to define their brand.  Brands are what market a company, therefore the better the brand and its relevance to target group, the more popular the company will be. For instance a fashion corporations like VF and kellwood have established their own unique brands. Customers like to be associated with certain brands thus the need to be unique and creative. Also, another thing to note is that brands need to be unique otherwise, they will be sued by th owner for rights infringement.
VF Corporation is a fashion company that majors in sportswear brands. VF company specialize and targets the outdoor and sports people. The company owns several outdoor jeans wear, footwear and sportswear. Some of their popular brands include but are not limited to Timberland, Vans, Wrangler, lee among others. Kellwood on the other hand specializes in  ladies wear. Some brands associated with Kellwood include “Rebecca Taylor”, “Parker”, “Delvin”, “Xoxo” and “Democracy”. Both of the companies have specialized in certain niche and target market. Each of them knows their target market well therefore making it easier to produce quality products.
Among the strategies used to ensure the brands get the proper attention and popularity is the quality of products. In both of the companies, they have a dedicated staff that carries out research on methods and ways to ensure the customers comfort. The quality of the products is also among the key features taken seriously. Quality of a product distinguishes a brand from the others especially from the imitators.
In the fashion industry, the challenge faced usually comes from imitators. Alternatively, in order to fend them off, it is duty of the company to make authentic products. In addition to that, the company also need to create awareness. Failure to do so can defame the brand. Consequentially, the company will also make losses. For instance back In 2009, a fashion company lost over 1.5 billion shilling in revenue to imitators. Fighting of imitators can be challenging but also the efforts are rewarding.
 In fashion, creating a marketable and launching a brand is as essential as the business itself. As seen in the instance of Kellwood and VF, brand is what makes a company prosper. During brand creation, a company needs to identify its target market first. When a company develops a brand, they need to register and patent it in order to protects its right. Additionally, the name of the brand is also a factor in labellings your brands. A brand needs to have a captive name so that it attract customers and increase sales. Conclusively, the quality of a brand need to be uphold the standards of the company, otherwise people will distrust the brands associated with the company. </string>
</resources>
